<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Powerhouse</title><description>Powerhouse</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Powerhouse</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 3.30</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 07:52:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Mushrooms</title><description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to go search some mushrooms, since I should prove my basic survival skills talents. Just kidding. I had nothing substantial to eat today. But this red phallic mushroom was very interesting. I think I've read about it somewhere but forgot its name. Probably Devils finger or something like&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/mushrooms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5f453be2f0d0700515d66b9a</guid><dc:creator>Leonid Kovalenko</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 07:47:30 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://res-2.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4123.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://res-2.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4123.jpg" alt="Mushrooms"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided to go search some mushrooms, since I should prove my basic survival skills talents. Just kidding. I had nothing substantial to eat today. But this red phallic mushroom was very interesting. I think I've read about it somewhere but forgot its name. Probably Devils finger or something like that. Another interesting one is this sun shaped:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="https://res-1.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4125.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a place with a lot of birds bones. I thought it was some bird eater's lair. For some reason I made no pictures of this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then I encountered someones hut deep in the forest. It looked more like a land of several hut buildings. I decided not to make a visit. Just went to gather mushrooms as the sun was going down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And I was looking down all the way, so I have not noticed how got into some closed area. There was an abandoned bunker or something like that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="https://res-5.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4126.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="https://res-4.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4127.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Mushrooms"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Want to come in?&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm not coming in. Just going further and getting out of this area through the weakness in a spiky fence. Looks like this place been long forgotten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="https://res-2.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4129.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;I got a lot of brown cap boletuses from the lair, quite a lot of oilers from the bunker area. It got dark, and I went to the car.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Titled</title><description>&lt;p&gt;I used to update this website, trying to make those pictures showing up on mobile Safari. What is safari? Some kind of an african activity, I guess. Would be cool to attend one. Anyway, this website should mutate into something more meaningful with time. I would like to post some&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/titled/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5f3d4406fe17f40612817875</guid><dc:creator>Leonid Kovalenko</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 15:32:38 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://res-2.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4078.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://res-2.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4078.jpg" alt="Titled"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to update this website, trying to make those pictures showing up on mobile Safari. What is safari? Some kind of an african activity, I guess. Would be cool to attend one. Anyway, this website should mutate into something more meaningful with time. I would like to post some music. Lets see how far it can go.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Today</title><description>&lt;p&gt;I woke up and felt like a gloomy sky. I tried to record a voice for this track again and again. I was invited to the birthday party. But some people are also supposed to be there, whom I may know. So I'm confused and don't want anything new. Being&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5f37caef40df130534485032</guid><dc:creator>Leonid Kovalenko</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 12:24:57 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://res-2.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4062.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://res-2.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4062.jpg" alt="Today"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I woke up and felt like a gloomy sky. I tried to record a voice for this track again and again. I was invited to the birthday party. But some people are also supposed to be there, whom I may know. So I'm confused and don't want anything new. Being around people is difficult at times like this. Was asked to come, but want to say no. May be I should isolate and practice some confidence. But as the day goes I feel a bit better. So I decided to make a short visit and swam ahead like a leaky boat. I came when everyone started to leave. I'm not sure why. But does it matter. Just tried to record a voice for this track again and again ..&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>I'm tired</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is what you probably do not want to hear from me. But anyway, this is a text dump on the outskirts of life. I write whatever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel tired, especially at the first half of the day. This can manifest in the lack of energy, no purpose, and all&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/im-tired/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5f363d5bd0d97e0b3b5aac73</guid><dc:creator>Leonid Kovalenko</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 07:44:10 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://res-4.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_3945.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://res-4.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_3945.jpg" alt="I'm tired"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is what you probably do not want to hear from me. But anyway, this is a text dump on the outskirts of life. I write whatever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel tired, especially at the first half of the day. This can manifest in the lack of energy, no purpose, and all those kinds of things, they call a depression. This is true. I think it is a scourge of our time. I don't know, may be it is my own bubble, but some people told me they suffer from it. Practically most of the people I have a contact with have those kind of issues. And I think it is deep enough. You can admit it. But there are so many things today you can compensate with. I probably had it forever.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Experimenting</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Alright. This is my first message. I'm sitting in a minivan. Piles of garbage are around me. But I'm searching for my little tunnel in this existence.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/experimenting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5f34e4b9d0d97e0b3b5aac59</guid><dc:creator>Leonid Kovalenko</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 07:02:24 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="https://res-3.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4060.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="https://res-3.cloudinary.com/leokov/image/upload/q_auto/v1/powerhouse-images/IMG_4060.jpg" alt="Experimenting"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alright. This is my first message. I'm sitting in a minivan. Piles of garbage are around me. But I'm searching for my little tunnel in this existence.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>